export const chapter = "Chapter -12: Agreement of the verb with its Subject";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "What is the rule for verb and subject agreement regarding singular and plural subjects?",
          optionA:
            "Singular subjects take a plural verb; plural subjects take a singular verb.",
          optionB:
            "Singular subjects take a singular verb; plural subjects take a plural verb.",
          optionC: "Singular subjects and verbs do not need to agree.",
          correctAnswer:
            "Singular subjects take a singular verb; plural subjects take a plural verb.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which person does the singular first person represent in the text?",
          optionA: "Animals",
          optionB: "Plants",
          optionC: "The speaker",
          correctAnswer: "The speaker",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'He and she have gone together,' what is the subject?",
          optionA: "He",
          optionB: "She",
          optionC: "He and she",
          correctAnswer: "He and she",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct singular verb for the sentence 'You eat mango'?",
          optionA: "Eats",
          optionB: "Eat",
          optionC: "Eating",
          correctAnswer: "Eat",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which sentence demonstrates the correct usage of a plural subject and verb?",
          optionA: "I have a pen.",
          optionB: "We is players.",
          optionC: "We are players.",
          correctAnswer: "We are players.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Kiran and Simar are friends,' what is the number of the verb?",
          optionA: "Singular",
          optionB: "Plural",
          optionC: "Both A and B",
          correctAnswer: "Plural",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct singular verb for the sentence 'They eat mangoes'?",
          optionA: "Eat",
          optionB: "Eats",
          optionC: "Eating",
          correctAnswer: "Eats",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which person does the singular third person represent in the text?",
          optionA: "The speaker",
          optionB: "Animals",
          optionC: "Someone being spoken to",
          correctAnswer: "Someone being spoken to",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct plural verb for the sentence 'I am a player'?",
          optionA: "Am",
          optionB: "Is",
          optionC: "Are",
          correctAnswer: "Are",
        },
        {
          question:
            "According to the text, what happens if two singular subjects are joined as a subject?",
          optionA: "The verb remains singular.",
          optionB: "The verb becomes plural.",
          optionC: "There is no specific rule for this situation.",
          correctAnswer: "The verb becomes plural.",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "A Singular Subject _______ a Singular Verb and a Plural Subject _______ a Plural Verb.",
          optionA: "takes, takes",
          optionB: "takes, is taking",
          optionC: "is taking, takes",
          correctAnswer: "takes, takes",
        },
        {
          question:
            "First Person _______ with the pronouns 'I,' 'me,' and 'my.'",
          optionA: "associates",
          optionB: "relates",
          optionC: "corresponds",
          correctAnswer: "associates",
        },
        {
          question: "Singular Subjects and Verbs: 'He/She/It _______ mango.'",
          optionA: "eat",
          optionB: "eats",
          optionC: "eating",
          correctAnswer: "eats",
        },
        {
          question: "Plural Subjects and Verbs: 'We _______ mangoes.'",
          optionA: "eats",
          optionB: "eating",
          optionC: "eat",
          correctAnswer: "eat",
        },
        {
          question:
            "If two Singular Subjects are joined as a Subject, the Verb _______ in the Plural.",
          optionA: "are",
          optionB: "is",
          optionC: "be",
          correctAnswer: "is",
        },
        {
          question: "Singular First Person: '_______ a player.'",
          optionA: "I am",
          optionB: "I is",
          optionC: "Am I",
          correctAnswer: "I am",
        },
        {
          question: "Plural Subjects and Verbs: 'They _______ mangoes.'",
          optionA: "eats",
          optionB: "eat",
          optionC: "eating",
          correctAnswer: "eat",
        },
        {
          question: "Third Person: 'He/She/It _______ a pen.'",
          optionA: "have",
          optionB: "has",
          optionC: "having",
          correctAnswer: "has",
        },
        {
          question:
            "If two Singular Subjects are joined as a Subject, the Verb _______ in the Plural; for example: 'Kiran and Simar _______ friends.'",
          optionA: "is",
          optionB: "are",
          optionC: "be",
          correctAnswer: "are",
        },
        {
          question: "Singular Third Person: '_______ a player.'",
          optionA: "He is",
          optionB: "He have",
          optionC: "Is he",
          correctAnswer: "He is",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "A Singular Subject always takes a Singular Verb and a Plural Subject takes a Plural Verb.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Two Singular Subjects joined as a Subject will result in a Singular Verb.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Singular First Person refers to pronouns like 'I,' 'me,' and 'my.'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Plural Subjects and Verbs: 'They eat mangoes.'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "If two Singular Subjects are joined as a Subject, the Verb will be in the Plural.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Singular Third Person is represented by pronouns 'He/She/It.'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Plural Subjects and Verbs: 'We is players.'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'He and she have gone together,' the subjects are Singular.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Singular First Person: 'Am I a player?'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Plural Subjects and Verbs: 'We have pens.'",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
